Finding Aid for School of Education (University of Michigan) Records, 1904-2012
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Dean's Files
  - Berger, Carl F., 1958-1988; 1983-1988
    - Reports
      - Faculty Productivity 1985-86, 1986 (Box 40)
      - Graduate Studies in the School of Education: A Report to the Horace Rackham school of Graduate Studies, 1986 (Box 40)
      - The Impending Shortage of K-12 Teachers and Administrators in Michigan, 1986 (Box 40)
      - Instructional Technology in the School of Education by Kozma & Baggett, (discussion draft), 1988 (Box 40)
      - The Intellectual and Social History of Education, a Report on Education 691-692, 1986 (Box 40)
      - Planning and Development, Task Force on Institutional Policy of, 1984 (Box 40)
      - A Report on the Offering of Graduate Credit for Professional Development Activities, 1983 (Box 40)
    - Research, 1983-1987 (Box 40)
    - Research Centers, 1985-1987 (Box 40)
    - Research, Measurement, and Evaluation, 1986-1988 (Box 40)
    - Saginaw Public Schools, 1987 (Box 40)
    - Salaries, 1984-1988 (Box 40)
    - School Psychology, 1987 (Box 40)
    - Science Education Center, 1984-1987 (Box 40)
    - Senate Advisory Committee, 1984 (Box 40)
    - Shady Trails Camp, 1984-1986 (Box 40)
    - Social, Personal and Institutional Relationships of Education and Technology (SPIRET) Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 40)
    - Special Education, 1984-1986 (Box 40)
    - Special Education Commission, 1987-1988 (Box 40)
    - Speech and Hearing Sciences, 1983-1985 (Box 40)
    - Speech and Language Pathology Program (SLP)
      - General
        - 1985-1986 (Box 40)
        - 1987 (Box 40)
      - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 40)
      - Possible Discontinuance, 1987 (Box 40)
      - Site Visit, Report on, 1985 (Box 40)
    - Spencer Fellowship Program, 1983-1984 (Box 40)
    - Spring/Summer Sessions, 1983-1986 (Box 40)
    - Strategic Planning Retreat (Box 41)
      - 1987, 2 folders (Box 41)
      - 1988 (Box 41)
    - Student Grievance and Discipline Procedures, 1986 (Box 41)
    - Student Initiated Combined Degree Programs, 1988 (Box 41)
    - Student Quality Index and Student Information, 1987 (Box 46)
    - Students Unified Pre-Professional Organization Regarding Teaching (SUPPORT), 1988 (Box 41)
    - Superintendents Study Group Meeting, 1988 (Box 41)
    - Task Force on Teacher/Administrator Preparedness, 1986 (Box 41)
    - Teacher Certification
      - 1986-1987 (Box 41)
      - 1988 (Box 41)
    - Teacher Education
      - 1984-1986 (Box 41)
      - 1987-1988 (Box 41)
    - Teacher Education Conference, 1986 (Box 41)
    - Teacher Training Programs (re: accreditation), 1986 (Box 41)
    - Technical Education, 1984-1985 (Box 41)
    - Technology in Education, 1988 (Box 41)
    - Transition Team
      - General, 1985-1986 (Box 41)
      - Charge to the Task Force, 1983/84 (Box 41)
      - Expertise Roles (by program), 1984 (Box 41)
      - Faculty Workshop, 1984 (Box 41)
      - Final Evaluation Report, 1984 (Box 41)
      - Meeting Notes, 1983/84 (Box 41)
      - Reports to Faculty, 1983 (Box 41)
      - Transition Plan (volume 1), 1984 (Box 41)
    - Undergraduate School of Education Student Organization (USESO), 1986-1988 (Box 41)
    - University of Michigan Dearborn
      - 1983-1987 (Box 41)
      - 1988 (Box 41)
    - Urban, Technological and Environmental Planning (UTEP), 1986 (Box 41)
    - CSHPE Planning, 1985 (Box 49)
      [ER RESTRICTED until July 1, 2031 ]
    - Profiles on UM Faculty Interested in PSE Research, Organization, & Management, 1983-1984 (Box 49)
    - Research Center Directors Meetings, 1986 (Box 49)
    - SOE Catalog, 1986 (Box 49)
    - Strategic Planning, 1987 (Box 49)
    - Transition Team Documents, 1983-1984; 3 folders (Box 49)
  - Cecil Miskel, 1985-1998
    - Academic Affairs, 1996-1997 (Box 50)
    - Annual Fund, 1993-1998 (Box 50)
    - College Resources Analysis System, 1998 (Box 50)
    - Correspondence (email), 1995 (Box 50)
    - Correspondence (email), 1995-1996 (Box 50)
    - Correspondence (email) Claire and Ron, 1995 (Box 50)
    - CSHPE Newsletters, 1986-1993 (Box 50)
    - CSHPE Research Seminars, 1985-1991 (Box 50)
    - CSHPE Staff Agendas and Minutes, 1985-1991 (Box 50)
    - CSHPE Transition Meeting, 1989-1990 (Box 50)
    - Dean's Council, 1996 (Box 50)
    - Dean's Council, 1997 (Box 50)
    - Dean's Council, 1997-1998 (Box 50)
    - Decisions Made by the SOE Executive Committee During 9/26/1995 Meeting (Box 50)
    - Detroit Public Schools -- A Center for Innovation in K-12 Schools, 1996 (Box 50)
    - Dissertations, 1997-1998 (Box 50)
    - Dissertation Policy and Guidelines, 1990-1991 (Box 50)
    - Editors, 1997-1998 (Box 50)
    - Education Administration Planning, 1996-1997 (Box 50)
    - Educational Studies Program, 1996-1997 (Box 50)
    - Educational Studies Program, 1997-1998 (Box 50)
    - Educational Studies Program Student Handbook, 1997-1998 (Box 50)
    - Enrollment, 1996-1997 (Box 50)
    - Faculty Meeting, 1995 (Box 50)
    - Fall Faculty Reception/Dinners, 1996-1997 (Box 50)
    - Graduate Studies in Education Administration and Policy, 1996-1998 (Box 50)
    - HACE/CSHPE Development Materials, 1992-1995 (Box 50)
    - Informal Faculty Meeting Notes, May --, June, 1995 (Box 50)
    - Letters from Cecil, 1996-1997 (Box 50)
    - Letters from Cecil, 1997-1998 (Box 50)
    - Letters to Cecil, 1996-1997 (Box 50)
    - Letters to Cecil, 1997-1998 (Box 50)
    - Multimedia Classroom, 1997-1998 (Box 51)
    - National Center for Postsecondary Improvement, 1997-1998 (Box 51)
    - National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education (NCATE), 1996-1998 (Box 51)
    - NCA, 1996-1998 (Box 51)
    - News and Info Services, 1997 (Box 51)
    - OERI, 1997 (Box 51)
    - Office of Orientation, 1996-1997 (Box 51)
    - OMSA (Office of Minority Student Affairs), 1996-1998 (Box 51)
    - Organizational Charts, 1997-1998 (Box 51)
    - Pattishall Award, 1997-1998 (Box 51)
    - Peace Corps Dewitt Wallace RFP, 1997 (Box 51)
    - Peace Corps Fellows, 1997 (Box 51)
    - Peace Corps Fellows, 1997-1998 (Box 51)
    - Peace Corps General Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 51)
    - PhD Reinstatement Proposal Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 51)
    - Phi Delta Kappa, 1998 (Box 51)
    - Planning Meetings, 1995 (Box 51)
    - Presidential Inauguration, 1997 (Box 51)
    - President's Office, 1996-1997 (Box 51)
    - President's Office, 1997-1998 (Box 51)
    - Publication Requests and Survey Info, 1997 (Box 51)
    - Rackham Merit Fellows, 1997-1998 (Box 51)
    - Rackham Non-Traditional Fellowship, 1994 (Box 51)
    - Rackham School of Graduate Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 51)
    - Rackham School Graduate Studies, 1997-1998 (Box 51)
    - Regents Meeting RE: Faculty, 1997 (Box 51)
    - Research Activities, 1996-1997 (Box 51)
    - Research Activities, 1997-1998 (Box 51)
    - Research Incentive Program I, 1997-1998 (Box 51)
    - Retirees Reception, 1997 (Box 51)
      (See photographs in box 42)
    - Retirement Ceremony -- C. Philip Kearney, 1998 (Box 51)
    - Retirement Party -- Dorothy Ristenbatt, 1997 (Box 51)
    - RMF Students, 1998 (Box 51)
    - Situational Analysis, 1995 (Box 51)
    - SOE Alumni Board of Governors, 1997-1998 (Box 51)
    - SOE Alumni Fall Gathering, 1996 (Box 51)
    - Summer Art Fair Break, 1996 (Box 51)
    - TEAC Working Documents, 1997-1998 (Box 51)
    - Themes for Faculty Employment, 1996 (Box 51)
    - UM Dearborn, 1998 (Box 51)
    - UM Honors Convocation, 1996 (Box 51)
    - UM Office of Development, 1996-1998 (Box 51)
    - UM Office of the Registrar SOE Course Catalog, 1997-1998 (Box 51)
    - UNCF William Gray Breakfast, 1996 (Box 51)
    - Welcome and Academic Panel, 1996 (Box 51)
    - Faculty Search, 1995 (Box 54)
    - Faculty Search -- Director of Teacher Education, 1995-1997 (Box 54)
    - Faculty Search Info, 1997-1998 (Box 54)
    - Faculty Searches, 1997-1998 (Box 54)
    - Sabbatical Requests, 1995-1996 (Box 54)
    - Sabbatical Requests, 1996-1997 (Box 54)
    - Sabbatical SOE Request, 1997-1998 (Box 54)
    - TEAC Search, 1997-1998 (Box 54)
    - Faculty Search, 1995
    - Faculty Search -- Director of Teacher Education v, 1995-1997
    - Faculty Search Info, 1997-1998
  - Karen Wixson, 1972-2005; 1998-2005
    - Topical Files
      - A Guidebook for Feasibility Study and Campaign Planning, 2002 (Box 52)
      - Big 10 + Deans, 2002-2005 (Box 52)
      - Campaign Volunteer Leadership Convocation, 2001-2002 (Box 52)
      - Carnegie Delta Project, 2002 (Box 52)
      - Carnegie Initiative on Doctorate Proposal, 2002-2004 (Box 52)
      - Carnegie Scholars Program, 2004-2007 (Box 52)
      - CSHPE, 1999-2006 (Box 52)
      - CSHPE and School of Public Policy Joint Program, 2000 (Box 52)
      - Detroit Public Schools, 1999-2000 (Box 52)
      - Detroit Public Schools, 2000-2001 (Box 52)
      - Detroit Public Schools, 2001-2002 (Box 52)
      - Detroit Public Schools, 2002-2003 (Box 52)
      - Dual Degrees Business Administration, School of, 1999-2002 (Box 52)
      - Dual Degrees Business and Administration, 2002-2004 (Box 52)
      - Dual Degrees Education and Statistics, 2001 (Box 52)
      - Dual Degrees Education and Statistics, 2001 (Box 52)
      - Dual Degrees Higher Ed and Public Policy, 2000 (Box 52)
      - Director of Development Search, 2002-2007 (Box 52)
      - Educational Studies Program, 2001-2002 (Box 52)
      - English Language Institute, 2002 (Box 52)
      - Feasibility Study, 2003 (Box 52)
      - John Dewey Lecture, 2000-2004 (Box 52)
      - Kellogg Forum, 2001 (Box 52)
      - Kellogg Forum at UM, 2000-2002 (Box 52)
      - Kellogg Forum at UM -- Reports, 2002 (Box 52)
      - Kellogg Forum Meeting, 2000 (Box 52)
      - Kellogg Forum Proposal, 2001-2003 (Box 52)
      - Masters of Art and Certification, 2002 (Box 52)
      - National Reading Conference, 1997 (Box 52)
      - NCA, 1998 (Box 52)
      - Staffing -- CSHPE Searches, 1999-2000
      - Teacher Education Issues, 1998-2004 (Box 52)
      - U of M Campaign, 1998-2002 (Box 52)
      - Advising Info, 1986-1993 (Box 55)
      - Center for Research on Learning and Schooling, 1988-1992 (Box 55)
      - Combined Program in Education and Psychology (CPEP) Student Handbook, 1991-1992 (Box 55)
      - Competency Program for Reading Specialists, 1976- (Box 55)
      - Curriculum Teaching and Psychological Studies Program (CTPS), 1985-1986 (Box 55)
      - Educational Psychology Task Force, 1981-1985 (Box 55)
      - New Graduate Curriculum, 1991-1992 (Box 55)
      - Published Works, School of Education, 1974-1982 (Box 55)
      - Reading Certification (Box 55)
      - Reading Committee Minutes and Agendas, 1970-1971 (Box 55)
      - Reading Committee Minutes and Agendas, 1980-1982 (Box 55)
      - Reading Committee Materials, 1972-1981 (Box 55)
      - Reading Committee Memos, 1980-1984 (Box 55)
      - Reading Committee, Study Committee B, 1970-1974 (Box 55)
      - Reading and Literacy Correspondence and Memos, 1987 (Box 55)
      - Reading and Literacy Committee File, 1982-1986 (Box 55)
      - Reorganization, 1981 (Box 55)
      - School of Education Executive Education, 1991-1992 (Box 55)
      - School of Education Review and Program Reports, 1983-1986 (Box 55)
      - School of Education Transition Plan, 1984 (Box 55)
      - Special Education Program, 1983-1990 (Box 55)
      - Statements Regarding the Ph. D. and Ed. D., 1983-1990 (Box 55)
      - Teacher Education Task Force, 1990 (Box 55)
      - Training for Reading Specialists File, 1970-1993 (Box 55)
  - Deborah Ball, 2002-2010
    - A Strategic Assessment of the University of Michigan School of Education, 2010 (Box 52)
    - Challenges and Opportunities: Conversations about Immigration and Higher Education, 2007 (Box 52)
    - Combined Program in Education and Psychology (CPEP), 2006 (Box 52)
    - CSHPE 50th Anniversary Celebration, 2006 (Box 52)
    - CSHPE 50th Anniversary Materials, 2006-2007 (Box 52)
      (See DVD located in box 42)
    - Detroit Center, 2004-2007 (Box 52)
    - Dual Degrees Higher Ed and Business, 2007 (Box 52)
    - Dual Degrees Higher Ed and School of Medicine, 2008 (Box 52)
    - FY 2008 Certification of Financial Results and Internal Controls, 2008 (Box 52)
    - Task Force on Teacher Education Program Assessment, 2002-2009 (Box 52)
    - University of Michigan Summit, 2006 (Box 52)
  - Cecil Miskel, 1980-1998; 1988-1993
    - Academic Affairs
      - General Correspondence
        - 1988-1989 (Box 56)
          [ER RESTRICTED until November 1, 2035 ]
        - 1989-1990 (Box 56)
    - Academic Planning and Analysis
      - 1989 (Box 56)
      - Data, 1988 (Box 56)
    - Academic Program Group (APG)
      - Dean's Retreat Revisit, 9/10/1991; 12/03/1991 (Box 56)
      - Meeting, 11/25/1991 (Box 56)
    - Academic Record Project
      - 1988-1989 (Box 56)
      - Computerized Records, 1988 (Box 56)
    - Academic Services Board
      - Financial Aid Documents, 1989-1990 (Box 56)
      - General, 1989-1990 (Box 56)
      - Graduate Admissions Documents
        - 1989-1990 (Box 56)
        - 1990-1991 (Box 56)
      - Recruitment Documents, 1989-1990 (Box 56)
      - Teacher Education Documents, 1990-1991 (Box 56)
    - Academic Year, Review of, 1990-1991 (Box 56)
    - Administrative Services, Office of
      - 1989-1990 (Box 56)
      - Sue Taylor Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 56)
    - Admissions
      - 1989 (Box 56)
      - Graduate Applications, 1989-1990 (Box 56)
      - Graduate Application Statistics between Fall & Winter, 1991-1992 (Box 56)
      - Graduate Recruitment Day, 10/17/1998 (Box 56)
      - Undergraduate Admissions, Office of, 1991-1992 (Box 56)
    - Affirmative Action
      - Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 56)
      - Data, 1988-1989; 1989-1990 (Box 56)
      - General, 1986-1987; 1989-1990 (Box 56)
      - Harassment Policy, 1989-1990 (Box 56)
      - Memorandums, 1988-1989; 1989-1990 (Box 56)
    - Albom, Mitch, 9/19/1995 (Box 56)
    - Alumni
      - Development
        - 1989-1990, 2 folders (Box 56)
          [ER restricted until November 1, 2035 ]
        - Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 57)
        - Phonathon
          - 1990-1991 (Box 57)
          - 1989-1990 (Box 57)
      - Donor Reception (6/8/1994) (Box 57)
      - Education Alumni Society Board of Governors Meeting
        - 7/19/1989, 2 folders (Box 57)
        - 11/4/1989 (Box 57)
        - 7/18/1990 (Box 57)
        - 9/22/1990 (Box 57)
        - 1/19/1991 (Box 57)
        - 4/12/1991 (Box 57)
        - 7/24/1991 (Box 57)
        - 11/2/1991 (Box 57)
        - 1992-1993 (Box 57)
        - 4/2/1993 (Box 57)
        - 1993-1994 (Box 57)
        - 10/2/1993 (Box 57)
        - 1/15/1994 (Box 57)
        - 7/20/1994 (Box 57)
        - 1994-1995 (Box 57)
        - 1/21/1995 (Box 57)
        - 10/28/1995 (Box 57)
        - 3/23/1996 (Box 57)
        - Correspondence
          - 1991-1992 (Box 57)
          - 1993-1994 (Box 57)
          - 1994-1995 (Box 57)
      - Events
        - , 1989-Los Angeles, 9/21-9/24 (Box 57)
        - 6/17/1993 (Box 57)
        - 3/29/1995-Houston Reception (Box 57)
        - 2/10-18, 1996 (Box 57)
      - General Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 57)
      - Michigan Alumni Day Panel, 6/8/1993 (Box 57)
      - University of Michigan Alumni Association Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 57)
      - Visiting Team (Box 58)
        - 1991 (Box 58)
        - 1992 (Box 58)
    - America 2000 The President's Education Strategy, 1991-1992; 2 folders (Box 58)
    - American Association of Colleges for Teacher Education (AACTE)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 58)
      - Proposal, 1991 (Box 58)
      - Testimony and Supporting Materials, 1991 (Box 58)
    - American Association of University Professors, 1989-1994 (Box 58)
    - Ameritech
      - Bury, 11/11/1993 (Box 58)
      - Tech Linkages, 12/16/1993 (Box 58)
    - Angus Conference, 12/13-12/19; 1997 (Box 58)
    - School of Education Annual Reports, 1986-1993 (Box 58)
    - Art Fair Break, 7/19/1995 (Box 58)
    - Art, School of, 1990-1991 (Box 58)
    - Associate Dean Position Announcement, 1991-1992 (Box 58)
    - Awards
      - Faculty Teaching, Service, Merit, Etc., 1988-1989; 1989-1990 (Box 58)
      - General Awards Information
        - 1988-1989 (Box 58)
        - 1989-1990 (Box 58)
        - 1990-1991 (Box 58)
      - Ceremony
        - 1988-1989 (Box 58)
        - 1989-1990 (Box 58)
        - 1990-1991 (Box 58)
        - April 2, 1993 (Box 58)
        - April 15, 1994 (Box 58)
        - 1994-1995 (Box 58)
        - April 7, 1995 (Box 58)
        - Script, 1992 (Box 58)
      - Marguerite Wilker Johnson Committee Guidelines, 1980-1990 (Box 58)
    - Bangkok, 1990 (Box 58)
    - Bentley Historical Library, 1986-1987; 1988-1989 (Box 58)
    - Berlin, Lawrence Associate Dean
      - Articles, 1989-1990 (Box 58)
      - Correspondence
        - 1989-1990 (Box 58)
        - 1990-1991, 4 folders (Box 58)
        - 1991-1992, 3 folders (Box 59)
    - Brown vs. Board of Education of Topeka, Kansas -- Commemoration, 6/3/1995 (Box 59)
    - Budget
      - 1991-1992 (Box 59)
      - 1992-1993, 2 folders (Box 59)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 59)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 59)
      - Conference, 2/20/1991 (Box 59)
      - Correspondence
        - 1989-1990 (Box 59)
        - 1990-1991 (Box 59)
        - 1991-1992 (Box 59)
      - Data Tables, 1994-1995 (Box 59)
      - Financial Matters, 1991-1992 (Box 59)
      - General Documents, 1988-1989; 1989-1990 (Box 59)
      - Hearing, 1994-1995 (Box 59)
      - Planning Meeting, 1/20/1993 (Box 59)
      - Priorities Committee
        - General, 1990-1991 (Box 59)
        - General Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 59)
        - Meeting, 2/20/1992 (Box 59)
      - Requests
        - 1988-1989, 1989-1990 (Box 59)
        - 1988-1991 (Box 59)
        - 1990-1991, 2 folders (Box 59)
        - 1991-1992, 2 folders (Box 59)
        - 1992-1993, 2 folders (Box 59)
        - 1993-1994 (Box 59)
        - 1994-1995 (Box 59)
        - Brochure, 1989-1990 (Box 59)
    - Building
      - 1994-1995 (Box 59)
      - General, 1987-1989 (Box 59)
      - Space Analysis
        - 2/9/1993 (Box 59)
        - 4/23/1993 (Box 59)
        - Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 59)
    - Burbles, Nick Presentation, 6/11/1993 (Box 60)
    - Bureau of Accreditation and School Improvement Studies (BASIS)
      - Undated (Box 60)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 60)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 60)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 60)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 60)
      - Budget Meeting, 4/25/1991 (Box 60)
    - Bushaw, Bill, 8/13/1990 (Box 60)
    - Business Administration, School of, 1989-1990 (Box 60)
    - Bylaw Revisions
      - 1984-1985 (Box 60)
      - 1985 (Box 60)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 60)
    - Career Planning and Placement, 1988-1989 (Box 60)
    - Center for Afroamerican and African Studies (CAAS), 1988-1989; 1989-1990 (Box 60)
    - Center for Educational Improvement through Collaboration (CEIC), 1988-1989 (Box 60)
    - Center for Human Growth and Development
      - 1989-1990 (Box 60)
      - 8/30/1992 (Box 60)
    - Center for Near East/North African Studies, 1989-1990 (Box 60)
    - Center for Research on Learning and Schooling
      - 1987-1988 (Box 60)
      - 1988-1989, 2 folders (Box 60)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 60)
      - 1989-1990-Lawrence (Box 60)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 60)
      - Budget Meeting, 1991 (Box 60)
      - Faculty Meeting with Cecil Miskel, 5/24/1989 (Box 60)
      - Meeting "Retreat", 1989-1990 (Box 60)
    - Center for Research on Learning and Teaching (CRLT)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 60)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 60)
    - Center for Science Teaching and Learning
      - 1990-1991 (Box 60)
      - Group Meeting, 9/22/1992 (Box 60)
      - Research Team-Joe Krajcik, 1991-1992 (Box 60)
    - Center for the Study of Higher and Postsecondary Education (CSHPE)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 60)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 60)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 60)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 60)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 60)
      - Annual Reports, 1986-1987; 1987-1988 (Box 60)
      - Faculty Reviews, 7/13/1995 (Box 60)
    - Ceremony Marshal, 1992-1993 (Box 61)
    - Charter Schools
      - Meeting with Duderstadt, 3/13/1995 (Box 61)
      - Susette Jaquette, 5/24/1995 (Box 61)
    - Children's Center, 1988-1989 (Box 61)
    - Citizens' Education Committee
      - 1988-1989 (Box 61)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 61)
    - Combined Program in Education and Psychology
      - 1988-1989 (Box 61)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 61)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 61)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 61)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 61)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 61)
    - Commencement
      - Winter, 1988 (Box 61)
      - Winter, 1989 (Box 61)
      - Spring, 1990 (Box 61)
      - Winter, 1990 (Box 61)
      - Spring, 1992 (Box 61)
      - Spring, 1993 (Box 61)
      - Winter, 1993 (Box 61)
      - Spring, 1994 (Box 61)
      - 1994 (Box 61)
      - Spring, 1995 (Box 61)
      - 1996, 2 folders (Box 61)
      - Exercises
        - School of Education, 5/2/1992 (Box 61)
        - University, 5/2/1992 (Box 61)
    - Committee on International Studies
      - 1988-1989 (Box 61)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 61)
    - Community College Consortium, 1988-1989 (Box 61)
    - Computers
      - Accounts, 1987-1988 (Box 61)
      - Allocation, 1987-1988 (Box 61)
      - Computing Center, 1988-1989 (Box 61)
      - Funds, 1987-1988 (Box 61)
    - Computers in Early Literacy (CIEL)
      - 1987-1988 (Box 61)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 61)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 61)
    - Congressional Briefing, 2/5/1999 (Box 62)
    - Confer, 1989-1990 (Box 62)
    - Convocation
      - 1989 (Box 62)
      - 1990 (Box 62)
      - 3/24/1991 (Box 62)
      - Fall, 9/9/1992 (Box 62)
      - Fall, 9/8/1993 (Box 62)
      - Fall, 8/7/1994 (Box 62)
    - Correspondence
      - 1989-1990 (Box 62)
      - 1989-1990, 1990-1991 (Box 62)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 62)
      - Congratulations to Faculty from Students and Others, Cecil's Responses, 1991-1992 (Box 62)
      - Declines by Cecil Miskel for Invitations for Positions in other Universities, 1989-1990 (Box 62)
      - Email
        - 1992-1993 (Box 62)
        - 1993-1994 (Box 62)
        - 1994-1995 (Box 62)
      - Letters from
        - 1988-1989 (Box 62)
        - 1989-1990 (Box 62)
        - 1990-1991 (Box 62)
        - 1991-1992 (Box 62)
        - 1992-1993 (Box 62)
      - Letters from Cecil to Provost and Vice President for Academic Affairs, 1990-1991 (Box 62)
      - Letters to
        - 1988-1989 (Box 62)
        - 1989-1990 (Box 62)
        - 1990-1991 (Box 63)
        - 1991-1992 (Box 63)
        - 1992-1993 (Box 63)
      - Thank You Letters from Cecil Miskel for letter of congratulations on appointment as Dean of Education, 1988-1989 (Box 63)
      - Thank You letters to Cecil Miskel for his letters of recommendation or nomination, 1988-1989; 1989-1990 (Box 63)
    - Council for Undergraduate Affairs, 1989-1990 (Box 63)
    - Courses
      - Core
        - 1989-1990 (Box 63)
        - 1990-1991 (Box 63)
        - 1994-1995 (Box 63)
      - Enrollment
        - Winter, 1989 (Box 63)
        - Spring/Summer, 1989 (Box 63)
        - Fall, 1989 (Box 63)
        - Winter, 1990 (Box 63)
        - Spring/Summer, 1990 (Box 63)
        - Fall, 1990 (Box 63)
        - Winter, 1991 (Box 63)
        - Spring/Summer, 1991 (Box 63)
      - Information, 1988-1989 (Box 63)
    - Curriculum Teaching and Psychology Studies (CTPS)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 63)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 63)
    - Daly, Josephine, 5/17/1995 (Box 63)
    - Dean's Council
      - 1989-1990 (Box 63)
      - Meeting, 5/9/1990 (Box 63)
    - Dearborn, University of Michigan
      - 1988-1989 (Box 63)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 63)
    - Department of Public Safety and Security, 1989-1990 (Box 63)
    - Dey, Eric, 1990-1991 (Box 63)
    - Northern Detroit Area Event, 8/29/1991 (Box 64)
    - Development-School of Education
      - 1988-1989 (Box 64)
      - Correspondence